<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Misc. Notes on 4lch4's Homepage</title><link>https://4lch4.com/notes/misc/</link><description>Recent content in Misc. Notes on 4lch4's Homepage</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://4lch4.com/notes/misc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Razer Green Color</title><link>https://4lch4.com/notes/misc/razergreen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://4lch4.com/notes/misc/razergreen/</guid><description> Razer Green Color I&amp;rsquo;ve always been fond of the green that Razer uses for their products so the following list is the color in various formats. Hex — #47E10C RGB — rgb(71, 225, 12) HSL — hsl(103, 90%, 46%) HWB — hwb(103, 5%, 12%) CMYX — cmyk(68%, 0%, 95%, 12%) NCOL — Y72, 5%, 12%</description></item><item><title>Leonardo Syndrome</title><link>https://4lch4.com/notes/misc/leonardo-syndrome/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://4lch4.com/notes/misc/leonardo-syndrome/</guid><description>Ever heard of Leonardo Syndrome?
If you’ve read Peter Burke’s excellent book, The Polymath,1 then you will have done, but if not: Leonardo Syndrome is where the drive to learn more and more results in beginning many projects but actually finishing few.2
It’s named ‘Leonardo Syndrome’ after Leonardo da Vinci himself. Despite being one of the most famous polymaths and creators in history - who doesn’t know about him?! - he was also somebody prone to failure.</description></item><item><title>The Future of the Web is on the Edge</title><link>https://4lch4.com/notes/misc/future-of-the-web/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://4lch4.com/notes/misc/future-of-the-web/</guid><description>October 6, 2022
Andy Jiang
FreshDeno Deploy
In the beginning, there was a single computer on a desk in a basement in Switzerland. It had a red-inked label:
32 years later, there are hundreds of millions of versions of that computer all around the world. Some are even powered down by default.
But developing for the web still feels as if there is only one machine. We develop as if our code is going to be deployed on a single instance of a server somewhere in a huge data center in Virginia, California, or Switzerland.</description></item></channel></rss>